Thanks for having me in your town. This
is a beautiful town. Beautiful scenery
around here.
And it's good because your red lights
are like 40 minutes long.
It's good that there's something to look
at. Why are they so long?
>> [laughter]
>> I got here yesterday and I was at a
light and I was like, "Oh, this is
beautiful."
This is crazy. This is good.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay, I'm good.
But it just kept This just stayed red.
Like the city was like, "No, look
longer."
Look at it longer.
It's beautiful.
>> [laughter]
>> It's good to be here to see you guys. I
was I had a flight from Tampa to Los
Angeles where I live a couple days ago
and I was checking into that flight. You
know they make you put your bag on there
and you weigh it. And that lady from the
airline looked at me and she goes, "So,
your bag
is over 50 lb.
And for safety reasons we can't put bags
in excess of 50 lb onto the flight."
So, I started to grab the bag. She goes,
"But
>> [laughter]
>> if you give us a hundred more dollars
>> we'll go ahead and throw it on the plane
for you."
I was like, "Well, that's great, but how
does that fix the safety issue
>> [laughter]
>> that you were just so concerned about?
Let me get this straight. If I give you
a hundred more dollars, you're going to
turn on the extra safety features of
this airplane."
>> [laughter]
>> I didn't know that's how it worked. They
shouldn't have gave me that kind of
information. We're about to take off.
Like starting to put your seat up. We're
about to take off. I just do a hundred
at a time. I was like, "Nope."
>> WOO!
>> HERE'S FIVE MORE. TRAY STAYS DOWN.
THE whole time.
I'm a tray down kind of guy.
>> [laughter]
>> Plane started taxiing out. I still had
my phone out. She had some match come
running down the aisle. She said, "Sir,
you need to put your phone away. The
signal from your phone can interfere
with the plane's steering. It could be
very I just threw my credit cards. Don't
you talk to me anymore.
>> [laughter]
>> Everybody gets Wi-Fi.
>> Don't worry about the signals, everyone.
I've paid extra for the safety package.
>> [laughter]
>> It's all good.
It's all good.
>> [laughter]
>> I recently got the TSA precheck.
Yeah.
It went straight to my head.
>> [laughter]
>> Now I go to the airport and I just pace
in front of the unchecked.
Look at you winding around all
unchecked.
>> [laughter]
>> You guys need to check yourself.
One guy who got really mad at me and
later turns out we were on the same
flight and we were boarding.
He got to board in front of me. He
walked by and right in my face he said,
"Group one."
>> [laughter]
>> Like I got like you've been there
before, buddy.
>> [laughter]
>> The flight from Tampa to LA was called
flight 10.
That was the name of it, flight 10. I
didn't feel very comfortable flying
across the country on flight 10.
Every flight I've ever been on has been
a strong four-digit number.
>> [laughter]
>> It's like 1455. They check both engines
before that flight takes off.
Flight 10, that sounds like a test.
>> [laughter]
>> That sounds like there's just some guys
in the room trying some stuff, you know,
and it's not been going well.
>> [laughter]
>> It's like they're in a room like, "All
right, guys, flight nine, that was a
disaster."
>> [laughter]
>> You really need the wheels. You need the
wheels. You do.
You do. You don't need them for the
flying part, but you definitely need
them for the landing part. So, I was
kind of right.
>> [laughter]
>> Do any of you guys have any ideas for
flight 10? Who's turn is it? Who's got
an idea for flight 10? I got one.
What's that? 6-hour nonstop flight?
Okay, how about we put a quarter of a
tank ethanol fuel in it?
>> [laughter]
>> Play nothing on the speakers but Barack
Obama speeches, and let's see how far
flight 10 can go on corn juice and hope.
FLIGHT 10.
WHO CARES?
THIS IS SPIRIT AIRLINES FLIGHT 10. WHAT,
are we going to lose like two taxpayers?
Let's try some stuff.
Let's figure it out.
>> I always do like to ask though, anybody
here come from a high school that had a
unique team name? So, nothing that's
ever been used in like professional
sports, NFL, NBA, baseball. Just go
ahead and yeah, just don't tell it to
me, just cheer.
>> [laughter]
>> What was that? What was that?
The Buckaroos?
>> [laughter]
>> Everybody cheering just sounds like a
condescending dad. There you go,
Buckaroo.
>> [laughter]
[applause]
>> Even when you win it can't feel good.
Good job, buckaroo.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> What else what else do we have over
here?
>> Scars.
>> What's that? The scars?
>> Darts.
Darts.
>> Oh, the darts.
>> [laughter]
>> She did a little the darts.
Oh, okay, the pointy ones. All right,
yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> I
thought you meant the car.
>> [laughter]
>> That would be weirder. The darts.
>> The darts, okay. Just a second. We're
still
>> [laughter]
>> We're still talking about darts.
What what city are you from or or state?
What's that?
>> Kaysville, Utah.
>> Kaysville, Utah? Okay. All right.
Is that like a thing there?
>> [laughter]
>> That's number one on Trip Advisor for
Kaysville.
Do you have the best darts in Kaysville?
Is that a thing there?
No, no, the pointy ones.
>> [laughter]
[applause]
>> What else do we have?
What's that?
>> Beat digger.
>> [laughter]
>> That come from the cheap seats in the
balcony, of course.
>> [applause]
>> Is that how we earned our way here?
>> [laughter]
>> Where are you from that you dig beats?
>> Jordan High School. What's that?
Jordan High School? All right.
That's That's here, right?
>> [laughter]
>> This This is going all over the world,
so people aren't going to know.
It's like Jordan. It's just some guy.
>> [laughter]
>> Jordan likes beets. I don't know.
Over here, somebody raised their hand
politely. What was yours?
The russets?
Okay.
Some other guy just yelled his out. He's
like, "That's not interesting. Listen to
mine."
>> [laughter]
>> What's Okay. All right. All right.
Russets are potatoes. Okay.
>> [laughter]
>> Getting heckled by Wikipedia.
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> Usually when I get heckled, someone's
like, "Get off the stage." But you guys
are like, "Here's some useful
information."
>> [applause]
[laughter]
>> All right. Potatoes. [laughter]
What else? What else do we have?
The caveman? All right. Cool. Where are
you Where are you from?
American Fork. [laughter]
All right. I don't know a thing about
that.
Caveman, what else?
The Dons?
Spanish Fork.
>> [applause]
>> Feel like everyone here knows something
about me.
>> [laughter]
>> I don't understand all these utensil
cities.
>> [laughter]
>> The Criminals.
>> Are you from Spanish Fork, too?
>> [applause]
>> I'm just guessing. I'm glad I made sense
to you guys.
Anyone else not from here? No.
>> [laughter]
>> How about Is there a couple of What's
that?
Patriots. Cool. You weren't listening to
my question. All right.
I'm Chicago Fork. Right there.
>> [laughter]
>> Syrup Makers.
>> The Syrup Makers?
The rest of you quiet down for a second.
>> [laughter]
>> He is trying to help me out. Is that
what it is?
>> [laughter]
>> I'm from Georgia, so
>> You're from Georgia, of course. I love
the syrup from Georgia.
>> [laughter]
>> So matter-of-fact.
I thought you were going to be like,
"Obviously I'm from Canada."
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> She's like, "Russ it's yeah. Yeah."
I'm from Saudi Arabia.
Obviously.
>> [laughter]
>> So the Syrup Makers?
>> Yeah, Syrup Makers.
>> Okay. What was So what was your mascot?
Just like a really bored guy.
>> [laughter]
[applause]
>> If I could name a high school team, it'd
be the chameleons. Wouldn't that be
great?
Every game you just dress up like the
other team.
>> [applause and cheering]
>> The thing I love about about different
cultures is you can say something in a
different in different culture then it
means something different to Americans.
Like my Indian friend Balal. I'm leaving
the gym, I'm sweating, you know, I'm
trying to get in shape, trying to lose
my stomach. I want a six pack for
Christmas. And
he was coming in as I was leaving out.
He said, "I see you've been working
out."
>> [laughter]
>> I said, "Yeah, man, I'm trying to get it
together." He's
He said, "I just lost 13 KILOS MYSELF."
>> [laughter]
>> I SAID, "AND YOU'RE SMILING ABOUT IT?"
YOU LOSE 13 KILOS WHERE I'M FROM,
you better start packing YOUR BAGS,
OKAY?
I SEE SOME OF YOU DIDN'T FIND THE HUMOR
in that. I'm
I'm talking about drugs, ladies and
gentlemen.
Just don't do drugs. Don't
Don't.
I appreciate 70% of the audience
understanding and laughing at that.
The rest of y'all looking at me like
this isn't okay. This night I'm
Do drugs have caffeine in them? I'M NOT
>> [cheering]
[laughter]
>> I JUST GOT ALL THIS INFORMATION TODAY.
MY MIND is blown.
I [laughter] feel like I'm on a whole
'nother planet. I'm like, "No Starbucks
FOR YOU? WHAT?"
HOW ABOUT THE GRANDE? NO GRANDE?
>> [laughter]
>> FORGIVE ME, I'M STUPID.
I LAUGH ALL the time. You ever laugh so
hard you fart A LITTLE BIT?
AND IT SQUEEZE OUT.
You do that little dance to get the
smell away from you. LIKE,
"DON'T COME OVER HERE. PLEASE, DON'T
COME OVER HERE."
Smell bad.
I'm awful. I start aging, so I start
eating things that try to, you know, so
I can feel better, but it don't come out
too good.
>> [laughter]
>> I love vegetables, but I'm I can't drink
milk, and I'm lactose intolerant, and
>> [laughter]
>> God bless you. I mean,
never mind.
>> [laughter]
>> I was laying in the bed the other night,
and I farted, and it smelled so bad a
Febreze commercial came on.
>> [laughter]
>> I didn't even want to get up. I just
clutched the blanket like it was a
monster in the room. I was
Namaste.
>> [laughter]
>> You don't have to hold that in. You know
you can laugh out loud.
You're turning colors.
>> [laughter]
>> That's your third color. She was like,
"I'mma stay this way." You turning
colors.
>> [cheering]
>> I feel safe here.
>> [laughter]
>> I do. CAN I SAY THAT? LIKE,
I FEEL LIKE I CAN WALK DOWN THE STREET
HERE WITHOUT even being pulled over.
Like, I didn't
>> [laughter]
>> All right.
I'M SERIOUS. THIS IS A NICE TOWN, MAN.
The police are killing black men like
it's on their to-do list nowadays.
That's
So, wait. Oh, okay. I
I got to check THIS ONE OFF.
>> [laughter]
>> YOU LAUGHED A LITTLE TOO HARD AT THAT,
BROTHER.
I'm just serious. ANYWAY,
>> [laughter]
>> I LOVE THIS SIDE OF THE CROWD. THEY
LAUGH ALL the way. They should SHUT IT
UP.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> YOU BETTER LAUGH. TOMORROW IS NOT
PROMISED.
KIM JONG-UN, he got his finger on the
button. He ready. I don't know I don't
know I don't know his name, BUT HE
READY.
>> [laughter]
>> HIM AND TRUMP, they they battling it
out. Just get IN THE RING. FIGHT EACH
OTHER. DON'T LET LOOK, I JUST GOT MY
CREDIT RIGHT. I WANT TO LIVE, OKAY?
I WANT TO LIVE. I WANT GRANDBABIES AND
EVERYTHING. I WANT TO LIVE.
>> [laughter]
>> I WANT TO SEE SOME MORE COMEDY SHOWS
MYSELF. I'VE BEEN loving comedy since I
was a kid.
I used to try to sneak in the comedy
clubs when I was too young to get in. I
had to use my best friend's ID. My best
friend is the ugliest person I know.
>> [laughter]
>> He's so ugly. When I used his ID, I had
to make faces to pretend I was him.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm standing at the front of the club
holding up his ID.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> That's an ugly face, right
I did that on a flight the other day. I
was going to Miami and this lady was
burping her child. So, the child was
facing me. I WENT
AND THAT KID SAW ME AND SAID
>> [cheering]
[laughter]
>> THE MOTHER TURNED AROUND AND LOOKED AT
ME. I WAS LIKE, "I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
WRONG WITH your child."
>> [laughter]
>> I have no idea. Can you please turn him
around?
>> This happened in Seattle a few months
ago. A guy got killed on the interstate.
He was driving the wrong way down the
interstate and the police spokesman was
quoted as saying, "We don't know how
fast he was traveling." But the posted
speed limit on that section of highway
is 60 mph.
If you're driving the wrong way down the
interstate, all the speed limit signs
are silver.
>> [laughter]
>> I don't think speed's your biggest worry
at that point.
Hope I don't get a ticket.
>> [laughter]
>> I WAS FLIPPING THROUGH THE CHANNELS THE
OTHER NIGHT AND I CAME across a senior
golf tournament. I thought, "Who's
watching seniors play golf?
Who has that kind of time in your life?
You know what I would watch though?
Senior cage fighting.
>> [laughter]
>> I don't think I could sleep if I thought
that was on.
>> [laughter]
>> Couple of 20-year-olds in the cage,
they're going to fight again in a month.
Couple of 80-year-olds in there, that's
a death match.
Tap out, crap out, nap out. That's how
that's going.
>> [applause]
>> You ever see these kind of stories in
the news? Somebody gets killed, kind of
tragic circumstances. Maybe they were
rock climbing, fishing, skydiving, they
get killed. And people always say this,
I know they mean well. They go, "At
least he died doing something he loved."
Which to me is the cruelest irony of all
time.
Cuz if I told you I was going to teach
you how to fish. You're going to love
fishing. You're going to fish almost
every weekend for the next 30 years. But
eventually
you're going to fall off a boat and
drown.
You'd could go, "You know what? I think
I'll learn how to draw."
>> [laughter]
>> You want to be happy for somebody? Hope
they die doing something they hated.
Then they didn't have to finish.
>> [laughter]
>> I want to die on Thanksgiving weekend at
my in-laws' house.
>> [laughter]
>> Maybe I can ruin that weekend for them
one time.
>> [laughter]
[applause]
>> You ever hear I died under those
circumstances, I want you to be happy
for me.
>> [laughter]
>> Ah, that's great. He hated doing that.
I got invited to a '70s themed party
recently. So I went to the Goodwill
store to look for ugly plaid jacket, and
I found it. And as I got to the cash
register, I discovered that Goodwill
sells gift cards.
>> [laughter]
>> Let me repeat that one more time.
Goodwill sells gift cards.
When is it ever appropriate to give
or to receive a Goodwill gift card?
>> [laughter]
>> Hey, I have some spare money. Why don't
you buy yourself something? Nothing new,
of course.
>> [laughter]
>> But I'm guessing there's a used
Crock-Pot or a T-shirt worn by a
stranger in here with your name on it.
If you ever open a card and a Goodwill
gift card drops out of there,
might want to rethink the relationship.
>> [laughter]
>> Look, honey, dinner for two at THE FOOD
BANK.
THE GOODWILL STORE BY MY HOUSE LAST June
said 50% off Father's Day sale. Nothing
says, "I love you, Pops."
quite like, "Hey, Dad, jump in the car.
We don't want to pay full price for the
used stuff."
>> [laughter]
>> If my kids ever take me to Goodwill on
Father's Day, you know what I want for
Father's Day? I want some new kids.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm supposed to go to the Home Depot
this weekend. I am not looking forward
to that. I don't like going into the
Home Depot. You know what? Why have 12
checkout stands if you're never going to
open them all at once?
>> [laughter]
>> You ever seen them all open at once? No.
What set of circumstances has to occur?
>> [laughter]
>> Hey, I got an idea. How about Sunday
afternoon? There's 40 of us in this
line.
Now they make you scan your own things
in there. You know what I do? This is
brilliant. The machine gives you the
option of Spanish or English, right?
There's always somebody watching the
self-serve machines. I just hit Spanish
and go, "Hey, could you do this for me?"
>> [laughter]
>> They come over every time. They do it
for you.
They look at you like an idiot. It
doesn't matter. You know why? You're not
the one wearing the orange vest.
Guy got all finished. I said, "Gracias."
>> [laughter]
>> Me gusta el chaleco.
>> I have uh three children. I have two
sons and one daughter. And um they say
as teenagers that girls are a little
harder to parent than boys. And I think
I see someone clapping. Yes. I
Some of people in agreement. And I think
I think it's true because I think girls
are just adult women in training, right?
They have all the raw ingredients of
adult women. Disdain,
spite,
revenge,
>> [laughter]
>> great intelligence,
a few irrational thoughts.
>> [laughter]
>> You.
But they haven't yet learned how to use
their evil powers for GOOD YET.
RIGHT?
>> [cheering]
>> I KNOW.
>> [applause]
>> SO, AS TEENAGERS, THEY'RE JUST LIKE
THOSE WINDSOCK people in front of the
furniture store.
They go up, they go down. You don't know
when or why. Just
They look almost human, BUT THEY'RE NOT.
THEY'RE NOT.
NOW, THE BOYS, I WILL TELL YOU ARE A
LITTLE more to fun to hang out with as
teenage as teenagers, but they smell.
There's just a funk and I don't know why
cuz they shower a lot
>> [laughter]
>> for extended periods of time.
They should be clean is all I'm saying.
>> [laughter]
>> And I don't know if you know this about
teenagers' brains. I didn't know this
until I had three of them. Their frontal
lobes of their brains have not finished
forming together, okay? So, their brains
are actually in their skull just
floating AROUND IN THERE.
>> [screaming]
>> THEY'RE JUST FLOPPING AROUND. SO, what
you get particularly with the boy
teenagers is you get a good choice, a
good choice, a good choice, and then a
doofus, and then a good choice, and then
a doofus. And if you get two doofus
choices in a row, your insurance
PREMIUMS GO UP.
>> [applause]
>> HAPPENS.
MY UH MY OLDEST DOOFUS ACTUALLY, my
youngest doofus, I'll start with him. My
youngest doofus is a doomsday prepper.
Apparently, I've let him watch too many
episodes of The Walking Dead because
he's filling our basement with survival
supplies.
>> [laughter]
>> And at first I made fun of him and I
thought, well, oh, what if the zombies
really come? Our family's survival
depends on the choices of this
17-year-old boy.
So, we're just going to be in a basement
in Cumberland, Maine surviving off of
flaming hot Cheetos and
blue Mountain Dew
>> [laughter]
>> and reading a lot of Victoria's SECRET
CATALOGS.
>> [cheering]
[laughter]
>> MY OLDEST doofus is a junior in college.
And when I dropped him off at his
freshman year, I took him to get his
dorm room supplies before I dropped him
off, and we went to Bed Bath & Beyond.
He had never been to Bed, Bath, and
Beyond. Apparently, he thought the
sheets and towels just came with our
house.
So, we went in there, and we had this
list of dorm room things he needed. The
first thing he needed was extra-long
twin sheets. I'm like, "Okay, they've
got gray, white, or pink." He said, "I
want white." I said, "You're getting
gray."
We're just going to start off with the
color they're going to end up at at the
end of the school year.
>> [applause]
>> Put them in the buggy. And then he says
to me, "Wait, what's the thread count on
those?"
And I said, "Do you even know what
thread count means?" He said, "Yeah."
No.
>> [laughter]
>> But the highest is the best, right? I'm
like, "Okay, these are dorm room sheets.
They're not the best. They're the worst.
If the thread count is 12, you're lucky,
but it doesn't matter
because these sheets aren't coming back
to my house.
I don't want to see these sheets ever
again.
I don't want to know what happens on
these sheets for the next 9 months,
and I don't want to see them again. It
doesn't matter what the thread count is
at the bottom of the garbage dumpster.
Put them in there.
>> [applause]
>> So, the next thing we needed was a
pillow. I said, "Go get yourself a
pillow." So, he goes in and he goes
through all these pillows at Bed, Bath,
and Beyond, and he picks one out and he
goes, "I want this one. It's made of
organic bamboo fronds and baby gosling
feathers.
It's only $200."
I selected a different pillow.
I said, "You see this one? It's made
from polyester.
>> [laughter]
>> It's only $6.
And when you puke red Hawaiian Punch up
all over it,
it will be a lot less sad at the bottom
of the garbage dumpster.
Put it IN THE BUCKET.
>> [applause]
[cheering]
>> PUT IT IN THERE.
>> I THINK THE TOUGH THING ABOUT BEING A
STEP PARENT is I don't have that
built-in thing that birth parents have
that make them proud of every single
thing that their child does.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm proud of most of the things my kids
do cuz they're super cool kids, but I'm
not proud of everything. And people I
know that have babies are proud of
everything. I've had more than one
friend call me to brag about how early
their baby lifted its head up.
And to me, that's stupid to even
mention.
>> [laughter]
>> But more than one guy has called me and
been like, "Dude, guess what? My baby's
lifting its head up way before babies
normally lift their heads up.
We're We're probably going to have to
put her in a special school for girls
with strong necks or something like
that.
She's got chubby arms and chubby legs,
but her neck is ripped, bro.
>> [laughter]
>> We got to cut slits down the front of
all her onesies so she doesn't rip it
out when she flexes her giant baby neck.
I'm jealous of that level of pride. I
want to have that, you know?
Here's an example of what I'm talking
about. One of my girls came home from
school and she said, "We ran the mile in
gym today. Guess my time." I said, "I
don't know. Maybe like 9 minutes." And
then she said, "16 minutes."
>> [laughter]
>> Well, I would not have guessed that you
ran the whole time. That's a terrible
time for a mile run.
Did something go wrong? What
Was there someone playing defense on
your mile run?
Did you have to do your mile run through
a corn maze? What happened?
>> [laughter]
>> I believe teenagers are God's revenge on
mankind. I really do. I think I think
one day the good Lord was looking down
over his creation
and said, "Let's see how they like it to
create someone in their own image who
denies their existence."
>> [laughter]
[applause and cheering]
>> Cuz I have read the Bible more than
once, cover to cover, and it it never
mentions how old the devil was when he
rejected God's authority.
If I'm guessing an age, I'm saying 16.
>> [laughter]
>> Devil got his driver's license, drove to
Georgia. THAT'S ALL I KNOW.
>> [laughter]
[applause]
>> ONE HECK OF A FIDDLE PLAYER, BUDDY.
>> [laughter]
>> YOU can't argue with a 16-year-old. You
can't. They have three-word vocabulary.
That's it.
Is [snorts] a word.
>> [laughter]
>> You going to pass your history test?
What is it?
>> [laughter]
>> Is another word.
>> No, you can't spend the night at your
friend's house. You flunked the history
test.
>> [laughter]
>> And then that word whatever. Whatever
drove me insane. It affected my nerves.
Cuz when it would come out of their
mouths, I'd immediately boink them right
in the eyes.
Whatever. Stop that.
>> [laughter]
>> And get your little angels ready for
therapy. They're going.
This is America.
>> [laughter]
>> Your kid's going to lay on a couch at
some point in his life and blame you for
everything.
You might as well give him reasons going
in.
Don't stress about it. They're going to
do it.
I told my kids when they learn to write,
when you perceive an injustice in our
home, do us all a favor, write it down
and date it and I'll initial it for you.
I'll come. Well, when you're
middle-aged, my memory's not so good. We
could breeze through the therapeutic
process together.
>> [laughter]
>> I'll just hand that book to the
therapist.
All that stuff with my initials next to
it, I did and I'll be at THE GOLF
COURSE.
>> [laughter]
>> I DON'T GET IT. WHERE WE'RE AT AS A
NATION, WE got 40-year-old men calling
up their 65-year-old fathers and yelling
at them at 2:00 in the morning and
blaming them for all the grief in their
life. It may be true.
May have a rotten father, but at this
point in his life, what do you expect
him to do for you?
I got my answer ready. I'm waiting for
one of my sons to call me up at 2:00 in
the morning. You ruined my life. All I'm
going to SAY IS, "WHATEVER."
>> [clears throat]
>> WHAT OTHER ANSWER IS THERE?
DO-OVER? You know, "Well, we didn't mean
to ruin your life. Hey, why don't you
move back home? Me and Mom will re-raise
you."
Yeah, we're a lot calmer since our
strokes, don't you know?
>> [laughter]
>> We can't remember when bedtime is. We We
can't remember anything. You can You can
move home and help us find our shoes in
the morning. That'll be fun.
We can't find anything around here.
Remote controls, car keys. It's like a
scavenger hunt every day.
You sure do sound like a nice young man.
What was your name again?
>> My wife and I moved into an apartment
that has two bathrooms, which I think
already just adds another 5 years to our
marriage. Fact that we don't have to
compete for a shower in the morning. And
we never take a shower together.
Uh I think some people think that's
strange, but honestly, it's just not
practical for us. Because when you first
get together with somebody, the idea of
taking a shower together sounds awesome.
If a woman's like, "Hey, I'm I'm
thinking about taking a shower."
Uh hopefully not in that voice. I should
probably not have done that. That's
probably not
"Hey, you want to take a shower?"
Ask me.
>> [laughter]
>> It's very appealing when you first get
together, though.
But any guy here that lives with a woman
knows that if you try and take a shower
together, odds are it's just going to
turn into you standing in the back for
about 6 minutes. Just
>> [laughter]
>> It's freezing back here. It's really
cold. I I can see it's hot up there. I
can I can see the steam. That's where I
stand when I take a shower, quite
frankly, but
>> [laughter]
>> sweetie, but what happens though is the
water hits the top of your forehead
and it comes off as this cool side mist
and that's all I get to work with. I get
a little produce shower. This is going
to take forever for me to get
clean. Is it Is it my turn? All right,
fantastic. Cool. All right.
Here we go.
We're on different rinsing cycles. I
don't want to mess that up. Cool.
I don't recognize any of these but you
got to condition three times. All right,
I'll be right back there. That was warm.
Okay.
>> [laughter]
>> This is uh boring, actually. This
I know you're naked. That's cool. But if
I knew it was going to go this long, I
would have put my Kindle in a Ziploc or
something. I'm
>> [laughter]
>> Are you
Are you GETTING OUT? YOU'RE GETTING OUT.
COOL. YEAH.
TAKE BOTH TOWELS. I DON'T
I don't need both towels, either. This
We are out of hot water though,
sweetheart, so
It's all right. I'll just smell today.
That's all right.
>> [laughter]
>> I like her apartment. I like her
bathrooms. I have one gripe with her
bathroom though. And it's the way that
it's set up. It's configured in such a
way where when you're standing in the
shower and you pull back on the shower
curtain, that main mirror is right
there.
And I'm not usually ready for that.
Like it's normally if you're going to be
naked in front of a mirror, you kind of
psych yourself up a little bit, right?
You're just like, "All right, here comes
the mirror."
>> [laughter]
>> You just flex the whole time you're in
front. "Hey, you look pretty good today.
All right." Just brush your teeth. There
we go.
I'm putting my contact lens. All right.
All [laughter] right, you deserve a
pizza. Good for you. All right.
Somehow I forget every morning. I get
done with my shower, I turn off the
water, put my shampoo back,
pull back the shower curtain. I'd rather
see a puma in my bathroom
>> [laughter]
>> than my naked, disappointed, foggy self
looking back at me.
Also, whoever it was that designed the
mirror to go down to here,
we need to talk because
I've also discovered that kind of my
personal self-confidence in my body is
directly correlated to wherever I wrap
the towel around myself.
Like some dudes wrap it around here.
Stop it.
Uh
I like to go like right here. If I could
wrap it around my neck, that'd be
like like a cape poncho kind of thing.
That's
that's the look I'd like.
People give me a hard time because of my
appearance. This is how I I typically
dress.
People like, "Mike, why you always so
dressed up?"
I'm like, "I'm not dressed up.
This is just police repellent."
>> [laughter]
[applause]
>> I'm just saying I never fit the
description, YOU KNOW.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> OFFICER PULLED ME OVER. HE WAS LIKE, "IS
THAT A cardigan you GOT ON THERE?"
I NEED YOU TO SLOW DOWN, SIR.
I'm excited to be in the West. I'm from
South Carolina. I'm from a a town
Camden, South Carolina.
From the South. I tell people wherever I
go I'm from the South with a F and not a
T H.
FROM THE SOUTH.
ONE THING ABOUT SOUTHERNERS, WE have the
unique ability to just make up words,
you know.
It's in DNA.
We say words like finna and fixin.
What it happened was, that's one word.
Right there, that's one.
That's how it work.
My fact, my favorite word is a made up
word. It's five syllables.
One word.
What you not going to do.
Yeah, my mother said that a lot when I
was growing up.
My mother said stuff like, "What you not
going to do
is keep running in
>> [laughter]
>> and out of this house.
That's what you're not going to do.
What you're not going to do is stand in
front of that refrigerator
>> [laughter]
>> and hold that door open.
Little boy,
that's what you're not going to do.
Y'all can use it at your job. You know,
you go to work, you got that co-worker
that's always asking you questions
before you get settled. You're like,
"What you're not going to do is come in
here and ask me questions before I turn
on my computer. That's what you're not
going to do. That's
what you're not going to do.
We're unique in the South. Uh we we love
nicknames in the South.
I realize there's some people I've been
knowing my entire life.
I don't know their real names.
>> [laughter]
>> My brother called me the other day. He
said, "Hey man, you know Mark Davis's
mom passed away."
>> [laughter]
>> I said, "I don't know Mark Davis, man."
He's like, "Stinky, man. Stinky's mama
passed."
>> [laughter]
>> I was like, "Why you ain't say that from
the start?
>> [laughter]
>> I need to give Stinky a call."
You know, I think white dudes have the
coolest nicknames. I really do.
Cuz white dudes' nicknames go with them
their entire life.
White dudes have nicknames like Rusty,
Skip,
Chip.
Like your nickname could be Chip. You
could be the CEO
of a bank.
You could have Chip on your business
cards.
>> [laughter]
>> The brothers can't do that.
Pookie can't be a branch manager at the
bank.
You don't trust your money with Pookie.
>> [laughter]
>> They're like, "Right this way, Dr.
Junebug will see you."
I'm like, "No, he will not."
What you're not going to do is have me
in a room with a Dr. Junebug.
I said, "Thank you, Mama Doc, but I'm
not going to hell. That's not my
>> [laughter]
>> So, I've noticed this in the South, uh
they're building a lot of new homes and
subdivisions, but in some of the titles
of the neighborhoods, they have the word
plantation.
I don't know about you.
>> [laughter]
>> I can't live on a plantation.
We tried that already one time,
That didn't work out quite so well.
>> [laughter]
>> I was at the Parade of Homes with my
wife. They had something in the window I
wasn't familiar with, so I asked my
wife. I said, "Hey, what are those
called?"
She said, "Oh, those are called
plantation shutters."
I was like, "I guess we won't be getting
any of those."
The word plantation makes me shudder.
>> [laughter]
>> Y'all ain't got no freedom blinds up in
here?
No I Have a Dream drapes? Y'all Y'all
have any
No civil rights curtains nowhere around?
>> And by the way, I am a nerd. I am not a
geek. I am a nerd, not a geek. And
what's the difference, you say, between
a nerd and a geek? I actually have a
Venn diagram to show you.
>> [laughter]
>> I have lots of graphs and charts. Be
prepared.
It takes three things to be a nerd. You
have smart, socially awkward, and
obsessed. All three of those things fit
You're just laughing at the chart, sir.
Clearly, he's in marketing.
>> [laughter]
>> Smart, socially awkward, and obsessed,
you're a nerd. Geeks, on the other hand,
tend to be just smart and obsessed.
>> [laughter]
>> They're just Star Trek geeks, comic book
geeks. THEY GO TO CONVENTIONS. THEY GO
TO PUBLIC EVENTS, NOT NERDS. I'M NOT AT
A convention unless I'm working IT
support. That's the only reason I'm
there.
>> [laughter]
>> Up here, if you're smart and socially
awkward, uh you're a dork.
And we have all spent time in the dork
region.
And if you're socially awkward and
obsessed, uh you're a stalker. See how
that works?
THANK YOU.
I LOVE TO WATCH PEOPLE TRY TO FIGURE OUT
WHERE THEY ARE ON MY CHART.
I think I'm A DORK STALKER.
>> [laughter]
>> SO, WHAT DOES IT MEAN TO BE A NERD? CUZ
I'M A proud nerd. There's a couple
things you can tell if you're a nerd.
First of all, when it comes to formal
wear, if you're a nerd, we love cargo
pants.
Yeah, yeah, people are with me. I got my
cargo pants on right now, baby. I got
pockets everywhere. I love cargo I have
cargo underwear on. That's how much I
love cargo pants.
And by the way, really big nerds, really
big nerds, they're in cargo shorts.
>> [laughter]
>> Several
People are pointing each other Oh, yeah.
Doug Doug wears the cargo shorts.
>> [laughter]
>> And I defend cargo pants. I do. I think
they're superior. My wife is horrified
that I wear cargo pants. I did a cargo
pant analysis, okay?
Here's a regular pair of pants. That
much IS FUNCTIONAL THAT'S TOTALLY
USELESS PART OF THE PANT.
THERE is nothing That right there, that
is a great pair of pants. Look at that.
That's a great pair of pants.
Look at that. You could You could carry
your entire life in those pants.
You could keep an extra pair of pants in
a pocket of your pants.
>> [laughter]
>> You're prepared for anything.
What else do I mean to enter? We love
charts. I love charts. I love I collect
charts. And I like a chart that really
sums things up in like one visual
experience. A whole whole thing in one
chart. For example, here's what's going
to happen if you're making microwave
popcorn. Okay? Here's the number of
edible pieces here on the Y axis.
>> [laughter]
>> And on the X axis is the time. Right?
You're at 1 minute, 2 minutes, no pieces
have popped, right? Very quiet. Nothing
happening in the microwave.
At some point above 2 minutes, you don't
know exactly where, all pieces are
popped, all pieces are burnt.
Right? That happens every time, right?
Quiet, quiet, quiet.
It's all They're all popped.
The bag is on fire, the smoke alarm is
blaring, and your house will stink for
at least a week.
That is the experience.
And that window of edible popcorn that
is a 1 nanosecond.
>> [laughter]
>> You do not stand a chance.
SOME OF MY CHARTS, I DON'T know why
they're true, I just know from
experience that this is what happens.
This is my gym, the locker room I gym,
okay? I walk in, I am that blue dot
right there. I start to get changed.
Pretty much the minute I get all my
clothes off, 12 guys walk in and this is
where their lockers [laughter] are.
>> [laughter]
>> Does that not happen every single time?
Huge empty locker room, I'm surrounded
by naked guys within seconds.
Defies probability. That defies
probability. And speaking of
probability, basic probability says if
you flip a quarter a thousand times,
it'll land heads 500 times and tails 500
times. When there's standard deviation,
that's what will happen. I guarantee it.
And that will hold true for a quarter.
But not everything.
When my [snorts] son was little, he
loved jelly bread.
>> [laughter]
>> If you drop a piece of jelly bread a
thousand times
and parents know, you give your kid a
piece of jelly bread, it it hits the
floor, it's not going to land jelly side
up. No, that's not as messy. The messy
way, 800 times out of a thousand, you
get a break 200 times out of a thousand.
Right? Right, parents? Right?
>> [laughter]
>> And that's on a kitchen floor, right? If
you have a nice rug, forget it, you
don't stand a chance.
>> [laughter]
>> I've seen a piece of jelly bread get an
inch above a nice carpet hover and then
flip the other way.
>> [laughter]
>> It's a law of physics, jelly bread
physics.
Comedy is under attack. People get
offended and there's a new culture out
there who can get offended first and for
other people. And that's the weirdest
thing in the world. I had that at a show
I did once. There was a blind gentleman
in the front row and I was teasing the
blind guy and he was having a great
time. After the show, he said, "Most
people ignore that I'm even there. So,
thank you for making me feel like a part
of it." And that's where his head was
at. But during the show, I'm teasing the
blind guy and a woman in the back is
like, "Excuse me, I'm offended."
I'm like, [laughter]
"What? Why are you?" "Because don't talk
to him anymore. I'm offended for the
blind gentleman."
I'm like, "You're you're offended for he
he's laughing."
>> [laughter]
>> He's facing the wrong way, BUT HE'S
LAUGHING.
AND TO HIS CREDIT, THIS IS THE BEST
PART. I GO, "Do you know her?" He goes,
"I have never seen her a day IN MY
LIFE."
>> [cheering]
>> YES.
THAT GUY WAS A GOOD DUDE.
I blame I blame the next generation cuz
they're offended by everything now.
They've never been through a war, a
draft, anything. I'm part of that
generation too, but we got to knock off
the sensitivity. We have to because
honestly, they get offended now about
cyber bullies. That's the big thing.
Talk to any student, "What's the worst
problem you're facing?" "Cyber bullies.
It's horrible. They can pick on you on
the internet.
Oh, really?
Our generation had real bullies.
>> [laughter]
>> They pulled our real underwear up our
real butt crack.
It really hurt, you know.
You don't have to pull a Twitter out of
your Snapchat at the end of the school.
[laughter]
Cyber bullies.
>> [clears throat]
>> I got bullied a lot cuz I look like a
guy who can fight, but I can't. So, the
bully would naturally pick on me.
Ladies, don't be confused. These muscles
will not defend you.
>> [laughter]
>> These are for looks. These are designer
muscles. That's what these are. Yeah.
These are for Starbucks.
They're not for tai chi. They're for
chai tea. That's what you do with these.
Even the exercises I do cannot help me
in a fight. Like I do the CrossFit
stuff. You get those those battle ropes.
Have you seen those guys? I'm one of
them.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm good at that.
That's not going to help me in a fight.
Like with this dude.
The biggest dude in the room sat him in
the front, ruined the view for 14 rows
of CrossFit.
WHO SET THIS ROOM?
>> [cheering]
>> AND JUST TO MOCK YOU, HE PUT HIS HAIR
BIGGER. WHAT ARE you going to DO ABOUT
IT?
AND WE'RE NOT GOING TO DO ANYTHING.
LIKE IF HE CAME TO FIGHT ME, WHAT AM I
GOING TO DO? WAIT TILL I GET YOUR
SHOELACES.
THAT AIN'T EVEN GOING TO WORK CUZ HE'S
WEARING SANDALS. GIVE ME THIS THING
RIGHT HERE. GIVE ME THE
I AM DEFENSELESS AGAINST THIS MAN.
>> [applause]
>> HE'S A GOOD SPORT, RIGHT?
MY THING IS I CAN'T DEAL WITH STUPIDITY.
I hate that, you know.
I had a a friend that said something so
stupid one time I told him we couldn't
even be cool no more.
>> [laughter]
>> Here's the thing. I I like I told y'all
I'm scared of spiders. That's true. I
really am. And like sometimes when it
gets hot outside like in the summer,
I'll get spiders in my car. I never know
how they get in there. It always freaks
me out. One day, I'm I'm riding around
in my car. I pulled up on my friend and
I saw some spider webs in the car. I
jumped out freaking out. I'm like, "Man,
I do not know how these spiders keep
getting in my car."
Now he looked at me with a straight
face. He going to help me out. He like,
"You got spiders in your car? Okay."
He like, "Are you LOCKING YOUR DOORS?"
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> THIS WAS SO STUPID IT MADE ME STUPID. I
answered him. I'm like, "You know what?
I DON'T THINK I DID, DUDE. THAT WAS A
>> [laughter]
>> HAVE YOU EVER HAD THAT HAPPEN to you?
Somebody say something so stupid it make
you think you stupid?
I'm in a Wendy's drive-thru one day,
okay? I'm in the drive-thru
trying to order my food. The lady came
over the speaker. She said, "Welcome to
Wendy's. Is this going to be for here or
to go?"
>> [laughter]
>> I just drove off. I'm like, "They must
They must be doing something new over
here. I don't
Don't like stupidity, man.
>> [laughter]
>> Like racism. I think racism is the
dumbest thing ever. Doesn't make sense.
You don't like somebody because of the
color of their skin. That's That's
stupid. I always tell people, "Sit down
and talk to somebody you don't know.
Learn about them. Get to know them." Our
country would be better if we all
treated each other like that. You know
WHAT I MEAN?
>> [applause]
>> JUST TRY IT.
THAT'S RIGHT. I CAN GUARANTEE IF YOU SIT
DOWN and get to know somebody, you'll
find a thousand other reasons to hate
this person
>> [laughter]
>> other than the color of their skin. You
know what I mean? Just Just earn the
hate is all I'm saying. Put the work in.
Earn the hate. That's
>> [laughter]
>> I don't have that issue, man.
I hang with everybody.
I like when I hang out with with my my
white friends.
Especially if I'm like the only black
person around.
>> [clears throat]
>> Kind of like now.
>> [laughter]
>> No, I like it. Especially like we're in
the car and I'm the only black person in
the car. I like to be in there cuz I
like to mess with them. Right. So, if
we're in the car and I'm the only black
person in the car, sometimes I'll I'll
breathe on the window and write help.
THEY GET MAD, BUT IT'S FUNNY TO ME, MAN.
>> [laughter]
>> I'M just saying, man.
I don't I don't get racism.
It's just so many other good reasons to
hate people.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm going to tell you what I don't like.
I don't like people that text and drive.
You seen people doing this, texting and
driving? That is the Listen, if you are
doing it, please stop cuz you can kill
somebody, all right? I was I was on the
interstate one day and I had my kids in
the backseat. I see this car swerving
all over the interstate. Closer I get to
the car, I see it's a dude and he's
texting on his phone. And he's doing
that thing where he's so into it, he's
like texting with both hands and trying
to drive with his knee.
I lost it, you know, cuz that's
dangerous. I got my kids in the
backseat. Now, he's swerving all over
the interstate. One time he swerved so
hard, he almost hit us. So, I had to
swerve to keep him from hitting us. That
made me spill my tequila. I'm like, "Yo,
this is so [laughter]
So, I had to call the police. Like, "Yo,
that was top shelf. You should come get
him." [laughter]
Very irresponsible.
>> College was different though, and
professors the college professors, they
never said it was there was no such
thing as a stupid question. You know
why? Because they knew better than that.
You don't get to be a college professor
and still hold the belief there's no
such thing as a stupid question, you
know.
So, in college I needed a different
strategy, a different tactic because I
didn't want to study or do the
assignments or anything like that. So,
I'd come up with smart questions that
would make me sound smart to the
teachers, you know, so when they were
giving the grades they might think,
"Hey."
So, I'd have to be like, "Yes, uh
Professor, after perusing the copious
reading assignments which you
ungrudgingly designate as compulsory,
it has become abundantly clear to me
that the incipient and might I say
pandemic rise of quantitative easing
in the post-holographic arena
spawns a situation and in fact a
conundrum
in which the widespread growth of
existential and even dystopian paradigms
will threaten to dominate the landscape
for the foreseeable future.
>> [laughter]
>> Now, having said that, how would you
therefore postulate a quid pro quo
complexification
from a nihilistic standpoint?
And being broadly contemporaneous, would
that postulation even be germane to the
philosophical dogma of the period?"
>> [applause]
>> And secondly,
because this is this is really a
two-part question.
>> [laughter]
>> Didn't like math. Math was Math was me
my least favorite subject. Do you like
school? You in school? You got it.
You're in school now? What's your name?
>> Chanel.
>> Chanel? What are you studying?
>> Nursing.
>> Nursing?
Yeah.
I studied doctoring for doctoring
doctoring.
What do they call it? Medicine.
>> [laughter]
>> It was a lot. It's a lot. I dropped out
after 2 years of high school.
No, I didn't like being a doctor. I was
a doctor for 1 day.
Yeah, everybody complains about
everything and I was like, "I can't do
this."
No, I didn't I couldn't I I didn't like
math. Math was my least favorite
subject.
Actually, it's like a five-way tie for
my least favorite subject, but math is
in there.
>> [laughter]
>> You know what I mean? Think about math.
I hate I hated math. Think about math
was you could try you could try try to
pay attention just look out the window
for 2 minutes, come back and you're lost
forever.
>> [laughter]
>> You might as well just look out the
window again cuz
you're never going to get back on track.
>> [laughter]
>> It's not like you can say to the
teacher, "Yes, could you just Could you
repeat that? Yeah, cuz I I was staring
out the window.
I saw the birds flying and I was
thinking, 'Gosh, what if I could fly?'"
Fly away, that's for sure.
Fly away from you and your lesson.
Your stupid lesson.
I
>> [laughter]
>> I was cool with counting.
Algebra Algebra 3, that was the worst
class ever. Algebra 3, remember? I
didn't actually take Algebra 3, I took
Algebra 1 three times.
But uh
that's addition.
But I was wrong back in the day. I would
tell the teacher, "I'm never going to
use this algebra stuff, right?" I always
use this algebra." But you don't use it
very much, but once in a while you use
algebra. Like a few months back, I was
in the train station in Baltimore and
train A was going to be leaving the
station at 5:00 p.m.
>> [laughter]
>> and traveling west at 80 miles per hour.
And train B was going to be leaving the
station 3 hours later on a parallel
track but going 100 miles per hour and
winds were out of the southeast at 18
miles per hour and it was a 30% chance
of rain.
The Dow Jones had dropped 200 points
that day
and the NASDAQ was up 40. I weighed 195
lbs and my blood pressure was 122 over
>> [laughter]
>> and the Kansas City Chiefs had a record
of eight and two and were at the top of
the leaderboard of the AFC West
and I had to figure out what train to
get on.
>> [laughter]
>> Luckily, there's an app for that now.
It's called CHOO CHOO.
>> [applause]
>> CHOO CHOO, c h u c h u. Just get the
free version, good enough.
One time we had a math test I got a
zero.
Zero percent.
Yeah, I'm not bragging, I'm just
My friend Kevin got a zero, too. He was
my study partner.
>> [laughter]
>> My other friend Terry got a one. Terry
got a one percent. We started calling
Terry the brain.
Started cheating off him a little bit.
>> [laughter]
>> Teachers Teachers always had the same
thing about cheating, right? They would
always say you're only cheating
yourselves, which is ridiculous. I mean,
if you didn't study, yeah, you cheated
yourself. But if they put the test in
the desk in front of you, and you
already didn't study, the only way
you're going to learn this stuff is if
you learn it off somebody else's paper.
I remember seeing like question number
seven, "What is the capital of Bolivia?"
Well, I don't know.
And now I'd like to learn it.
He doesn't know, either.
Stupid?
>> [laughter]
>> Stupido?
It's Pittsburgh.
Do we have any Middle Easterners here
tonight?
>> Yeah.
>> All right, looks like I'm skipping the
next joke, RIGHT?
I HAD TO MAKE SURE. WOO WOO.
IT ONLY TAKES ONE, ALL RIGHT? JK.
>> [cheering]
>> JK, EVERYBODY. WOO.
I like this.
>> [laughter]
>> I feel at home.
I like it.
>> [laughter]
>> Racism goes all the way, though. Like,
you know, people go, "Listen,
white people, you know, there's a lot of
racism against white people, too,
right?" Have you seen these
documentaries on serial killers? MY GOD.
>> [laughter]
>> EVERY EPISODE, OH, NO.
That's no good.
EVERYONE.
I BACK YOU UP.
>> [laughter]
>> I GOT YOUR BACK. I'M LIKE, YOU KNOW,
THIS is racist. Not all
white people are serial killers.
>> [laughter]
>> Problem is all serial KILLERS ARE WHITE.
AND THAT'S AS FAR AS I CAN GO.
What else can I do?
And it's not like it's white people's
fault. It's not like in your blood. It's
just white people are the only people in
the world that can be serial killers.
>> [laughter]
>> WHITE PEOPLE ARE the only PEOPLE IN THE
WORLD THAT CAN GET AWAY with eight
unsolved murders in a row. There's no
other ethnicity that can do that.
It's not your fault.
It's just you're the only one that can
do it.
SO, WHY NOT?
YOU DON'T THINK BLACK PEOPLE WANT TO BE
SERIAL KILLERS? OF COURSE, THEY DO.
THEY CAN'T.
COULD YOU IMAGINE A BLACK SERIAL He
would get pulled over on the way TO
GETTING SUPPLIES.
>> [laughter]
>> HE'LL JUST BE DRIVING, MINDING your own
business.
What seems to be the problem, officer?
Tail lights out. No, it's not. Officer
down. I mean, IS THAT
INDIANS, HISPANICS, ASIANS, we can't be
serial killers.
Our family's way too nosy.
MY MOM'S A SNITCH.
>> [laughter]
>> MY MOM WOULD SNIFF that out.
Where is the rope? What happened to the
duct tape? Where is the bleach? DAMN,
MOM.
GET OUT OF MY ROOM.
I'M TAKING YOUR TRUNK. YOU CAN'T GO IN
THE TRUNK. MOM, THERE'S PEOPLE IN THERE.
WHY ARE YOU doing this?
You raised me.
I like when people snort because I think
it reminds me of like the sound my dog
makes when he's running around like cuz
I got a dog. You got any dog people
here? Yeah, yeah, here we go. Right on.
My kind of folks, man.
Yeah, man, I love my dog. We have We got
a very eccentric dog, my wife and I. We
have a three-legged pug
named Taz.
That's a letter for each limb still
attached to his body.
>> [laughter]
>> We're praying we never have to call him
Mr. T.
>> [laughter]
>> And people always do what you guys did
when they hear we got a three-legged
dog. They're like, "Aw, that's so sweet.
You guys got a rescue." And I got to be
like, "Nah, we did it."
>> [laughter]
>> I'm still paying for that surgery.
>> And it's a boring story, man. He had a
birth defect. His elbow grew in
backwards, so he broke his leg. We had
to snip it. But we DIDN'T KNOW HE BROKE
HIS LEG FOR LIKE 3 MONTHS CUZ HE DIDN'T
SAY NOTHING.
WE JUST THOUGHT HE HAD A LITTLE SWAGGER
TO HIM. WE DIDN'T KNOW.
He's cool. He's hip. Let him be all
right.
>> [laughter]
>> But that's a boring story. I don't like
it.
It's not chivalrous. There's nothing
exciting about that. So what I like to
do is I like to mess with people. Folks
ask me what happened to his leg, I give
them a different answer every single
time.
Kids are the best. Oh my goodness, I
love it when kids come up. This little
boy come up to me one time. I was I had
my dog at the park. He's like, "Hey,
mister, what happened to your dog's
leg?" And I just went, "We lost it." And
I kept walking.
We were playing fetch and I threw it
hard. What do you want from me, kid?
>> [laughter]
>> I had one guy come up to me and say,
"Hey, what happened to your dog's leg?"
And I was like, "THE WAR."
>> [clears throat]
>> VIETNAM VET!
IN THE SENSE THAT HE WENT TO A
Vietnamese veterinarian.
>> [music]
[music]